[Music]
one of the biggest concerns for
everybody right now is the slowing down
of the economy and I think the
government now needs to increase
spending which will help kick-start
growth and the Finance Minister should
not bother about the fiscal deficit but
should be more interested in in fueling
growth so one way could be to actually
spend more in the rural sector like Mon
Riga and agriculture the other would be
on infrastructure these are the areas
that should be concentrated on the
corporate tax side I would want to
rationalize the rates of tax right now
we have three rates there is 34% there's
25% there's 17% we should move closer to
the 17% over a period of time without
exemptions the other thing that could
probably help would also to be to
abolish the dividend distribution tax
tax which is already paid by corporates
then in addition there is a dividend
distribution tax and then the recipient
also pays tax beyond ten lakhs of
dividend abolishing dividend
distribution tax could help a lot in
reducing or this inequity that is there
finally I would say on the overall
accounting I think there is a need to
move from cash accounting to accrual
accounting over a period of time and
that needs to be done to avoid the
fudging of the fiscal deficit that
happens with moving of cash from one
year to the other so these are some of
the measures that I would expect the
finance minister to consider in the
coming budget
[Music]
you